&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以我们要做的是一起做一个小实验。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So what we're gonna
do is a little experiment together.
事实证明，制作这个整洁图书馆的诺兰·劳森(Nolan Lawson)有一点
It turns out that Nolan Lawson,
who made this neat library, has a little
在应用程序中，您可以在一些不同的浏览器中进行尝试。
application where you can kind of go ahead
and try it out in some different browsers.
具有不同库的不同浏览器。
Different browsers with
different libraries.
所以我要你做的就是我们去这个网站
So what I want you to do is we're
gonna go to this website and
我们要带它去兜风。
we're gonna take it for a spin.
你要花大约五分钟来做这件事。
You're gonna spend about
five minutes doing this.
我们要做的就是打开它，
And what we're gonna do is
we're gonna open it up,
我们将尝试一些不同的库。
we're going to try out
some different libraries.
但我也想让你在一些不同的浏览器上尝试一下，对吗？
But what I'd also like you to do is try
it in some different browsers, right?
然后我们将在大约五分钟内讨论我们注意到的内容。
And then we'll talk about what we
noticed in about five minutes.